Meet Rana



Isanpur, Ahmedabad 9909781898 | meetrana2911@gmail.com

Personal Details

Date of Birth : 29/11/1999

Marital Status : SingleNationality : IndianGender : Male

Objective

Diploma Mechanical Engineer with the 2 year and 4 months experience in Quality Assurance department and as a recent graduate, i am seeking a role which allows me to continue learning and perfecting my skills as I provide high-quality work, and encourages me to flourish as a engineer.

Experience

Rane NSK Steering Systems Pvt. Ltd.

24/01/2022 - 16/04/2022

Engineer Intern

- Basic usage of Microsoft word and Microsoft Excel for data entry.
- Standard Operating Process preparation.
- Problem Solving through Quality Circle Approch.
- Basic knowledge about maintained and organized all records, documentation, and other files associated with quality engineering and inspection tasks.
- Rane NSK Steering Systems Pvt. Ltd.

15/07/2019 - 30/11/2021

- Diploma Engineer Trainee
 - Made quality decisions based on provided control outlines.
 - Accepted or rejected product samples after full quality engineering inspection.
 - Performed routine quality inspection operations using Various Measuring instruments.
 - Removed and documented all rejected product samples in the appropriate log books.
 - 5s Methodology.

Education

Gujarat Technological University

BE/B.Tech in Mechanical engineering 7.7 CGPA

2019-2022

Gujarat Technological University

Diploma in Mechanical engineering 8.5 CGPA

2015-2018

· Gujarat State Education Board

Class 10 73.33%

2014-2015

Skills

- Leadership
- · Self motivated
- Problem Solving
- Decision making
- · Detail oriented
- Team work

Achievements & Awards

- Certificate for :fundamental knowledge of E-commerce" by EMPI business school,Delhi
- Certificate for "foundations of business and entrepreneurship" by skill front.
- Certificate for 100 Activity points for "excellence beyond education" by Gujarat Technological University

Languages

- Gujarati
- Hindi
- English